June 23, 2018

To whom it may concern:

I had the pleasure of getting to know Michelle Adelufosi while she was an independent marketing contractor for Suncoast Social. We are a crafty social and inbound marketing agency located in Sarasota, FL. And we work with customers to create the kind of marketing that people truly love.

In addition, to just being a pleasant and knowledgeable professional to work with. Michelle developed hands on experience in the following areas in HubSpot which consisted of our agency's social media marketing, content management, web analytics, landing pages and search engine optimization. She was also very instrumental in promoting our agency's inbound marketing concepts, through our own marketing such as blogs and social media.

Michelle also developed and sustained our social media accounts, and content by utilizing HubSpot and keeping track of our analytics and inbound marketing. Through the regular maintenance of a variety of social media accounts, Michelle helped us to keep updated information available to a large number of clients and potential clients.

In conclusion, I would highly recommend Michelle's work highly and without reservation for an agency that is trying to enlarge its marketing presence with creative and considerable maintenance.

Should you require any additional information, feel free to contact me at 571-345-5448 or by email at ted@suncoastsocial.com and I will be happy to tell you more.

Sincerely,

Ted Smoot Founder & President Suncoast Social, LLC

MICHELLE ADELUFOSI

michelleadelufosi0@gmail.com, Cell (813) 454-1355 Arlington, VA

QUALIFICATIONS

Highly creative **Professional** with expertise in various technologies.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tableau, Pardot, Marketo, Adobe Experience Manager/Adobe Campaign Manager, Node.JS, CRM/Sprinklr, Creative Cloud, Magento, MVC, .NET Web API, Ruby and Rails, Python, Shopify, Adobe Analytics, Angular, Luminate Online, Linux, Magento, Convio, LMS, CMS, Scrum, JIRA, PHP, SQL, CSS, UberConference, Blackboard, Canvas, Captivate, Articulate Storyline, Camtasia, Squarespace, Salesforce, SharePoint, Eventbrite, Hootsuite, Slack, Drupal, Constant Contact, HubSpot, Asana, Basecamp, Keynote, SurveyMonkey, GitHub/Git, Google Docs, Google Analytics/Tag Manager, SEO, GoToMeeting, Yelp, GoToWebinar, Instagram, Pinterest, Mailchimp, Vine, Tumblr, Raisers Edge, BlogSpot, Skype, YouTube, Google+, QuickBooks, Microsoft Word, Excel, Dreamweaver, Outlook, Access, Rapid Entry, PowerPoint, Scan Speed, Isynergy, Compass, Adobe Acrobat, Publisher, Twitter, LinkedIn, Facebook, Snapchat, InDesign, Illustrator, HTML/JavaScript, WordPress, FileMaker, Quark, PageMaker, Photoshop, Business Plan Pro, Google AdWords (internet research), proficient on a PC/MAC, Ten Key Calculator, Word Processing 50 wpm

EDUCATION

Certificate, Google Analytics, October 2018 Udemy.com, Online

Active Public Trust Clearance, October 2018

Master of Science, Instructional Technology, May 2017 St. Thomas University, Online/Miami, Florida

Certificate, Social Media, February 2012 Hootsuite University, Online

Certificate, Volunteer Management, November 2011

Nonprofit Leadership Center, Tampa, FL

Bachelor of Arts, Communications/Interpersonal and Organizational, August 2008 University of South Florida, Tampa, Florida

Associate of Arts, Graphic Design, June 2004 International Academy of Design and Technology, Tampa, Florida

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Content Coordinator/Developer Contractor, Creative Circle Staffing Agency, Remote, Jan 2019 to March 2019 (freelance basis) Client: Erickson Living

- Analyzes web performance through use of visitor segmentation and marketing attribution
- Creates custom reports and dashboards on an ad hoc basis
- Works as a Drupal developer to develop content management using Drupal, HTML5 and other web methodologies on cloud environment

WORK EXPERIENCE (continued)

- Assists with Drupal custom module and custom theme development and advanced content management functionality
- Leverages responsive web frameworks to consistently complete product deliverables ahead of schedule
- Implements necessary changes to make website PCI compliant
- Set up and administered web servers and server software utilizing PHP
- Maintained project documentation
- Oversaw the day-to-day operation of computer networks including hardware/software support, training, and special projects

Google Analyst Manager Contractor, Isymmetry Staffing Agency, Falls Church, VA, Oct 2018 to Dec 2018, Client: CTAC

- Configured Google Analytics dashboard
- Distributed reports and provided insightful and meaningful feedback and recommendations to stakeholders
- Integrated Google Analytics metrics into CMS system content, especially Drupal and WordPress
- Proactively identify opportunities for site improvements and create business case with profit impacts
- Created periodic and on-demand reports and guide analysts to create such reports
- Utilized Google Analytics to track visitor flow and interaction throughout the company website
- Worked with Adobe product team to set up the base installation and configuration and involved in setting up a cloud-based hosting platform and configure as per business needs to meet the product and marketing goals.
- Write, edit, and develop web site content in Adobe Experience Manager

Web Marketing Coordinator Contractor, Hirestrategy Staffing Agency, Gaithersburg, MD June 2018 to Sept 2018, Client: Humane Society

- Performed measurement and analysis of website and projects for client
- Engaged in daily content creation and editing tasks in JIRA, GitHub and Drupal
- Contributed to and facilities the implementation of global and regional policies and practices pertaining to website development
- Gathered user feedback for website improvement and enhancements
- Maintained efficient communication between all internal and external stakeholders
- Provided daily maintenance of ecommerce dealer and consumer web sites utilizing PHP
- Monitoring, maintenance, and creation of MSSQL server tables

Marketing Consultant/Web Developer Contractor, Virtual Oct 2012 to current for various clients/agencies

Clients: Image Works and Suncoast Social

- Experienced in content design, targeting audiences, creating and executing double opt-in processes for landing pages using Adobe Campaign.
- Involved in integrating AEM with each of the campaigns for real time marketing and scalability enhancements and to show improvements in distributed marketing of local entities.
- Integrated Campaigns with AEM in order to manage email delivery content and forms directly in Adobe Experience Manager.
- Strong functional proficiency in campaign orchestration and marketing automation using Adobe Campaign.
- Involved in creating, executing and managing ongoing optimization process using Adobe Target.

WORK EXPERIENCE (continued)

- Troubleshot and resolved bugs in .NET/Node.JS applications to ensure optimal development environment.
- Optimized data for performance and efficiency purposes.
- Developed web pages using ASP.NET, HTML, PHP and used JavaScript for styling the web pages.
- In-depth knowledge of developing web applications using ASP.NET web forms, ASP.NET MVC.
- Increased front-end efficiency by transferring the blogs over to WordPress and brand-associated them with the main site.
- Provide varied web services including consultation, domain registration, research and set-up of hosting, usability testing, design, site architecture, content organization and editing, coding, database integration, testing and site maintenance. Specializing in content management systems (CMS Made Simple / WordPress) and Magento eCommerce.

Client: Multicultural Foodservice and Hospitality Alliance, Feb 2016 to current

Client: Self Reliance Center for Independent Living, Oct 2013 to June 2016

Client: Career Guy, June 2011 to Feb 2016

Client: Gaining Results, Inc., Feb 2011 to June 2016

- Manages social media platforms (Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn), including daily monitoring, posting, and content development
- Coordinate and implement social media marketing communication projects with responsibilities that include social media advertising, creating brand awareness online and website maintenance
- Prepare status reports on social media efforts and success rates/creates monthly E-News publication
- Instructs clients on social media and marketing campaigns also mentors them on best social media and marketing techniques
- Utilize Google Analytics to track visitor flow and interaction throughout the company website
- Provide analysis and insight regarding various online tools such as the site search, mobile site Instructs clients on social media and marketing campaigns also mentors them on best social media and marketing techniques
- Assigned tasks/collaborated with team members utilizing Asana
- Troubleshoot technical issues and imported tasks in Asana
- Supporting current websites, collaborating with development teams, managing client website projects, taking part in team meetings, and making sure development projects are completed in time.

Administrative/Social Media Assistant, University Area Community, Tampa, Florida, April 2012 to Oct 2013

- Entered youth information into a database and corresponds with site managers/liaisons
- Prepared minutes for meetings

- Managed social media platforms (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and YouTube), including daily monitoring, posting, and content development/sends email blast through Constant Contact
- Prepared status reports on social media efforts and success rates
- Coordinated and implement social media marketing communication projects with responsibilities that include social media advertising and creating brand awareness online
- Initiated conversation through forums, twitter and postings

May 5, 2019

Dear Hiring Manager:

I am interested in the Marketing Manager position. Please find my resume attached for your review and consideration. After earning my B.A. degree in Communications from the University of South Florida; I had the opportunity to stumble upon my true passion. I began to volunteer at American Red Cross and fell in love with the experience of making a difference in my community. Following this, I became a "perpetual" volunteer within several organizations and held my hand up high whenever help was needed. This love developed into a realization that my talents lie in the areas of leadership, web development, marketing and coding. And, I'm opened to relocating as well. Also certified as a social media consultant through Hootsuite University http://learn.hootsuite.com/u/msmedialist. In closing, I think it's important to share that because of my experience in marketing and fundraising support, I understand the importance of always developing capital and human resources. I feel confident that I could help to maintain and increase participation within your organization.

Thank you again, I can be reached at (813) 454-1355.

Sincerely,

Michelle Adelufosi

WordPress sites managed

http://self-reliance.org

https://srma.net

http://www.imageworkscreative.com

http://www.mfha.net

Blog for former client

http://cadprogrammermagazine.com/printingpress/?author=2

Social Media accounts managed

https://www.facebook.com/ImageWorksCreative

https://twitter.com/imageworks

https://www.facebook.com/MFHA.net/

https://twitter.com/mfhanet?lang=en

https://www.facebook.com/hitpromo

https://twitter.com/hitpromotional

https://www.instagram.com/hitpromotional/

https://www.facebook.com/CareerGuy

https://twitter.com/CareerGuy

http://www.linkedin.com/in/careerquy

https://twitter.com/univareacomm

http://www.facebook.com/pages/University-Area-Community/325448920854773

https://www.linkedin.com/company/university-area-community

http://www.linkedin.com/groups/University-Area-Community-2012-Nonprofit-4548126

https://www.facebook.com/pages/Self-Reliance-Center-for-Independent-Living/402416496475284?

ref=hl

https://twitter.com/SelfRelianceInc

https://twitter.com/AFPSuncoast https://www.facebook.com/pages/TampaBayJobLinks/530849133646581?ref=hl

https://twitter.com/TBJobLinks https://www.linkedin.com/company/tampabay-job-link